Guide to the Dennis Cooper Papers ca. 1970-2002 MSS 085
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Book projects and related materials
  - Subseries B: Book projects and related materials
    - Discontents, table of contents, undated (Box 5, Folder 143)
    - Discontents, introduction and acknowledgments, undated (Box 5, Folder 144)
    - Discontents, Steve Abbot, undated (Box 5, Folder 145)
    - Discontents, Dorothy Allison, undated (Box 5, Folder 146)
    - Discontents, Hilton Als, undated (Box 5, Folder 147)
    - Discontents, D.L. Alvarez, undated (Box 5, Folder 148)
    - Discontents, Brian Bouldrey, undated (Box 5, Folder 149)
    - Discontents, Elizabeth Brownrigg, undated (Box 5, Folder 150)
    - Discontents, Elizabeth Brownrigg cont., undated (Box 5, Folder 151)
    - Discontents, Pat Califia, undated (Box 5, Folder 152)
    - Discontents, Jelli Cleaver, undated (Box 5, Folder 153)
    - Discontents, Vaginal Creme Davis, undated (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - Discontents, Robert Glück, undated (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - Discontents, Richard Hawkins, undated (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - Discontents, Richard House, undated (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - Discontents, Hudson, undated (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - Discontents, Dennis Hunter, undated (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - Discontents, Bo Huston, undated (Box 5, Folder 160)
    - Discontents, Diviana Ingravallo, undated (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - Discontents, Michael Jones, undated (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - Discontents, Benjamin J. Keyser, undated (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - Discontents, Jeffrey Kennedy, undated (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - Discontents, Kevin Killian, undated (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - Discontents, Kate Knuth, undated (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - Discontents, Larry Bod, undated (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - Discontents, Eric Latzky, undated (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - Discontents, Craig Lee, undated (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - Discontents, Johnny Noxzema, undated (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - Discontents, Achy Obejas, undated (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - Discontents, Suzette Partido, undated (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - Discontents, Dale Peck, undated (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - Discontents, Robin Podolsky, undated (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - Discontents, Kathleen Ritchey, undated (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - Discontents, Sarah Schulman, undated (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - Discontents, David Sedaris, undated (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - Discontents, Ken Siman, undated (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - Discontents, Ana Maria Simo, undated (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - Discontents, Annie Sprinkle, undated (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - Discontents, David Trinidad, undated (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - Discontents, David Vernon, undated (Box 5, Folder 182)
    - Discontents, Matias Viegener, undated (Box 5, Folder 183)
    - Discontents, Danielle Willis, undated (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - Discontents, Untitled manuscripts, undated (Box 5, Folder 185)
    - Discontents, Correspondence, undated (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - Discontents, Publishing Agreement, undated (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - Discontents, Reviews, undated (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - Discontents, Press, undated (Box 5, Folder 189)
    - The Dream Police, Correspondence, undated (Box 5, Folder 190)
    - The Freed Weed, manuscript by Casey McKinney presented by Dennis Cooper, undated (Box 5, Folder 191)
    - The Freed Weed, manuscript by Casey McKinney presented by Dennis Cooper, undated (Box 5, Folder 192)
    - The Freed Weed, promotional material, undated (Box 5, Folder 193)
    - Knife/Tape/Rope, manuscript, undated (Box 5, Folder 194)
    - Knife/Tape/Rope; playbill, promotional material, photos, undated (Box 5, Folder 195)
    - Spew, correspondence, undated (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - Spew, Press, undated (Box 5, Folder 197)
    - Introduction to Powerless by Tim Dlugos, undated (Box 5, Folder 198)
    - Them: play, reviews, playbills, undated (Box 5, Folder 199)
    - They See God, reviews and promotional material, undated (Box 5, Folder 200)
    - Tricks, porno screenplay by Cooper and Yonemoto, undated (Box 5, Folder 201)
    - The Undead, manuscript, undated (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - The Undead, correspondence, undated (Box 5, Folder 203)
    - The Undead, business, undated (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - The Undead, reviews, undated (Box 5, Folder 205)
    - The Undead, promotional material, undated (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - The Undead; playbill, contact sheet, schedule, undated (Box 5, Folder 207)
    - The Undead, photos and negatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 208)
    - The Undead, CD and slides, undated (Box 5, Folder 209)
    - Weekly Poem, manuscript, undated (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - Weird Little Boy; manuscript by Cooper, McKinney, Blake and Zorn, undated (Box 5, Folder 211)
  - Subseries C: Collaborative Projects
    - Collaborations--Readings, undated (Box 5, Folder 212)
    - Collaborations with Houston-Jones, undated (Box 5, Folder 213)
    - Collaborations with Houston-Jones continued, undated (Box 5, Folder 214)
    - Collaborations--Untitled play by Haasen and Cooper, undated (Box 5, Folder 215)
- Series II: Book projects and correspondence of writers and artists
  - Steve Abbot, "American Gay Poetry", undated (Box 5, Folder 215a)
  - Steve Abbot, "Hidden Masters of the Beats", undated (Box 5, Folder 216)
  - Steve Abbot, "The Malcontent", undated (Box 5, Folder 217)
  - Steve Abbot, review of Cooper's poetry, undated (Box 5, Folder 217a)
  - Steve Abbot, Correspondence, undated (Box 5, Folder 218)
  - Kathy Acker, Correspondence, undated (Box 5, Folder 219)
  - Kathy Acker, on Acker by Cooper, undated (Box 5, Folder 219a)
  - Hilton Als, manuscript of review, undated (Box 5, Folder 219b)
  - Kenneth Anger, Correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 219c)
  - Gregg Araki, manuscript, undated (Box 5, Folder 220)
  - Gregg Araki, correspondence, undated (Box 5, Folder 221)
  - Gregg Araki, introduction on Araki by Cooper, undated (Box 5, Folder 221a)
  - Dodie Bellamy, Complicity, undated (Box 5, Folder 222)
  - Dodie Bellamy, "Digression as Power", undated (Box 5, Folder 222a)
  - Dodie Bellamy, A Good Clean Life, undated (Box 5, Folder 223)
  - Dodie Bellamy, Hallucinations, undated (Box 5, Folder 224)
  - Dodie Bellamy, Kong, undated (Box 5, Folder 225)
  - Dodie Bellamy, The Letters of Mina Harker, undated (Box 5, Folder 226)
  - Dodie Bellamy, Mina letter to Bill, undated (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - Dodie Bellamy, Mina letter to Cooper, undated (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - Dodie Bellamy, Mina letter to Dr. Van Helsing, undated (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - Dodie Bellamy, Mina letter to Sam, undated (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - Dodie Bellamy, "Mrs. America at the Congress of Dreams", undated (Box 6, Folder 231)
  - Dodie Bellamy, Reptilicus, undated (Box 6, Folder 232)
  - Dodie Bellamy, Untitled pieces, undated (Box 6, Folder 233)
  - Dodie Bellamy, correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 234)
  - Steve Benson, Briarcombe Paragraphs, undated (Box 6, Folder 236)
  - Steve Benson, Dominance, undated (Box 6, Folder 237)
  - Scott Benson, poem, undated (Box 16, Folder 235a)
  - Steve Benson, Poetry Flash, undated (Box 6, Folder 238)
  - Steve Benson, correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 239)
  - Laura Berringer, correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 239a)
  - Laura Berringer, photos, undated (Box 16, Folder 239b)
  - Bruce Boone, from Carmen, undated (Box 6, Folder 240)
  - Bruce Boone, "An Exchange of Letters", undated (Box 6, Folder 241)
  - Bruce Boone, "For Jack Spicer", undated (Box 16, Folder 241a)
  - Bruce Boone, "Gay Language", undated (Box 6, Folder 241b)
  - Bruce Boone, "George Bataille", undated (Box 6, Folder 242)
  - Bruce Boone, poems, undated (Box 6, Folder 243)
  - Bruce Boone, "Robin Blaser's New Syntax.", undated (Box 6, Folder 244)
  - Bruce Boone, "Sleep", undated (Box 6, Folder 245)
  - Bruce Boone, correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 246)
  - Bruce Boone, correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 246a)
  - Brian Bouldrey, "Everything But What You Need", undated (Box 6, Folder 246b)
  - Brian Bouldrey, "Guts, and No Glory", undated (Box 6, Folder 246c)
  - Joe Brainard, Nothing to Write, undated (Box 6, Folder 247)
  - Joe Brainard, reading announcement, undated (Box 6, Folder 248)
  - Joe Brainard, Recent Visitors, undated (Box 6, Folder 249)
  - Joe Brainard, correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 250)
  - Poppy Z, undated (Box 6, Folder 251)
  - Poppy Z, undated (Box 6, Folder 252)
  - Poppy Z, undated (Box 6, Folder 253)
  - Poppy Z, undated (Box 6, Folder 254)
  - Poppy Z, undated (Box 6, Folder 255)
  - Donald Britton, In the Empire, undated (Box 6, Folder 256)
  - Donald Britton, poems, undated (Box 6, Folder 257)
  - Donald Britton, correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 258)
  - Donald Britton, promotional material, review, business, undated (Box 6, Folder 259)
  - Bruce La Bruce, manuscript, undated (Box 16, Folder 259a)
  - Bruce La Bruce, Correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 259b)
  - (No folder), undated (Box 6, Folder 260)
  - (No folder), undated (Box 6, Folder 261)
  - Vija Celmins, reviews and promotional material, undated (Box 6, Folder 262)
  - Vija Celmins, correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 263)
  - Tom Clark, Life of., undated (Box 16, Folder 263a)
  - Tom Clark, poems, undated (Box 6, Folder 264)
  - Tom Clark, untitled manuscript, undated (Box 6, Folder 265)
  - Tom Clark, untitled manuscript, undated (Box 16, Folder 265a)
  - Tom Clark, promotional material, undated (Box 6, Folder 266)
  - Tom Clark, correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 267)
  - Tom Clark, photos, undated (Box 6, Folder 268)
  - Tom Clark, cover mock-up, undated (Box 6, Folder 269)
  - Kirby Congdon, manuscript, undated (Box 6, Folder 270)
  - Kirby Congdon, correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 271)
  - Kirby Congdon, reviews, undated (Box 6, Folder 272)
  - Dennis Cooper, endorsements, undated (Box 6, Folder 273)
  - Dennis Cooper, correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 274)
  - Christopher Cox, articles, undated (Box 6, Folder 275)
  - Christopher Cox, correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 276)
  - Christopher Cox, correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 276a)
  - Christopher Cox, invitation and clippings, undated (Box 6, Folder 277)
  - (No folder), undated (Box 6, Folder 278)
  - (No folder), undated (Box 6, Folder 279)
  - (No folder), undated (Box 6, Folder 280)
  - (No folder), undated (Box 6, Folder 281)
  - (No folder), undated (Box 6, Folder 282)
  - Sam D'Allesandro, The Zombie Pit, undated (Box 6, Folder 283)
  - Robert Davis, correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 283a)
  - Rob Dickerson, untitled manuscripts, undated (Box 16, Folder 283b)
  - Rob Dickerson, correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 283c)
  - Rob Dickerson, ephemera, undated (Box 16, Folder 283)
  - Rob Dickerson, photos, undated (Box 16, Folder 283e)
  - Time Dlugos, Fresh Air Fund letter, undated (Box 16, Folder 290a)
  - Tim Dlugos, "Gay Challenge to. ," "Lunch at St, undated (Box 6, Folder 284)
  - Tim Dlugos, "Generation", undated (Box 6, Folder 285)
  - Tim Dlugos, "Naked Brunch", undated (Box 6, Folder 286)
  - Tim Dlugos, poems, undated (Box 6, Folder 287)
  - Tim Dlugos, "Preserves", undated (Box 6, Folder 288)
  - Tim Dlugos, reviews, undated (Box 16, Folder 294a)
  - Tim Dlugos, Strong Place, undated (Box 6, Folder 289)
  - Tim Dlugos, "Village Leg", undated (Box 6, Folder 290)
  - Tim Dlugos, correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 291)
  - Tim Dlugos, reviews, undated (Box 6, Folder 292)
  - Tim Dlugos, Memorial Program, undated (Box 6, Folder 293)
  - Tim Dlugos, readings and announcements, undated (Box 6, Folder 294)
  - Tim Dlugos, photos, undated (Box 6, Folder 295)
  - Bret Easton Ellis, correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 296)
  - Kenward Elmslie, "A Tribute to K.E." by Michael Silverblatt, undated (Box 16, Folder 299a)
  - Kenward Elmslie, Lola, undated (Box 6, Folder 297)
  - Kenward Elmslie, promotional material, undated (Box 16, Folder 299b)
  - Kenward Elmslie, "Workshop Exercises", undated (Box 6, Folder 298)
  - Kenward Elmslie, correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 299)
  - Mark Ewert, various manuscripts and ephemera, undated (Box 16, Folder 307a)
  - Mark Ewert, correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 307b)
  - Mark Ewert, photos, undated (Box 16, Folder 307c)
  - Elaine Equi, The Corners of the Mouth, undated (Box 6, Folder 300)
  - Elaine Equi, Interview, undated (Box 6, Folder 301)
  - Elaine Equi, "Secrets", undated (Box 6, Folder 302)
  - Elaine Equi, "So What Else is New?", undated (Box 6, Folder 303)
  - Elaine Equi, "Underwear", undated (Box 6, Folder 304)
  - Elaine Equi, "Views Without Rooms", undated (Box 6, Folder 305)
  - Elaine Equi, correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 306)
  - Elaine Equi, promotional material and photos, undated (Box 6, Folder 307)
  - Fan Mail, undated (Box 6, Folder 308)
  - Fan Mail, undated (Box 6, Folder 308a)
  - Vincent Fecteau, correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 309)
  - Vincent Fecteau, promotional material, undated (Box 6, Folder 310)
  - Vincent Fecteau, photos, undated (Box 6, Folder 311)
  - Vincent Fecteau, slides, undated (Box 6, Folder 312)
  - Bob Flanagan, interview, undated (Box 6, Folder 313)
  - Bob Flanagan, correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 314)
  - Amy Gerstler, b/103, undated (Box 6, Folder 315)
  - Amy Gerstler, "The Bones of the Hand", undated (Box 6, Folder 316)
  - Amy Gerstler, "The Devil's Apartment", undated (Box 6, Folder 317)
  - Amy Gerstler, "Difficulty", undated (Box 6, Folder 318)
  - Amy Gerstler, "Dust", undated (Box 6, Folder 319)
  - Amy Gerstler, "Grave", undated (Box 6, Folder 320)
  - Amy Gerstler, "Grocery Store", undated (Box 6, Folder 321)
  - Amy Gerstler, "Headlines", undated (Box 6, Folder 322)
  - Amy Gerstler, "I'm Only Writing", undated (Box 6, Folder 323)
  - Amy Gerstler, "Intro", undated (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - Amy Gerstler, "Isabelle", undated (Box 6, Folder 325)
  - Amy Gerstler, "Lucky You", undated (Box 6, Folder 326)
  - Amy Gerstler, "Marriage", undated (Box 6, Folder 327)
  - Amy Gerstler, "Nature in Literature", undated (Box 6, Folder 328)
  - Amy Gerstler, Nerve Storm, undated (Box 6, Folder 329)
  - Amy Gerstler, "One", undated (Box 6, Folder 330)
  - Amy Gerstler, "Please", undated (Box 6, Folder 331)
  - Amy Gerstler, poems, undated (Box 6, Folder 332)
  - Amy Gerstler, poems, undated (Box 6, Folder 333)
  - Amy Gerstler, poems, undated (Box 6, Folder 334)
  - Amy Gerstler, poems, undated (Box 7, Folder 335)
  - Amy Gerstler, poems, undated (Box 7, Folder 336)
  - Amy Gerstler, poem by Gerstler and Cooper, undated (Box 7, Folder 337)
  - Amy Gerstler, review of Tom Clark's End of the Line, undated (Box 7, Folder 338)
  - Amy Gerstler, Script for four disembodied voices, undated (Box 7, Folder 339)
  - Amy Gerstler, Small Bed--manuscript, undated (Box 7, Folder 340)
  - Amy Gerstler, "Why I Am Convinced", undated (Box 7, Folder 341)
  - Amy Gerstler, Yonder--manuscript, undated (Box 7, Folder 342)
  - Amy Gerstler, correspondence, undated (Box 7, Folder 343)
  - Amy Gerstler, promotional material and cover art, undated (Box 7, Folder 344)
  - Amy Gerstler, reviews, undated (Box 7, Folder 345)
  - Allen Ginsberg, photo and correspondence, undated (Box 7, Folder 346)
  - Robert Glück, "Allegory", undated (Box 7, Folder 346a)
  - Robert Glück, review of Closer, undated (Box 7, Folder 346b)
  - Robert Glück, "Do You Think Lazarus", undated (Box 7, Folder 347)
  - Robert Glück, "Genre", undated (Box 7, Folder 348)
  - Robert Glück, "His Heart is a Lute Held Up", undated (Box 7, Folder 349)
  - Robert Glück, Jack the Modernist--manuscript, undated (Box 7, Folder 350)
  - Robert Glück, "Learning to Write/Bataille", undated (Box 7, Folder 351)
  - Robert Glück, "Learning to Write/Burroughs", undated (Box 7, Folder 352)
  - Robert Glück, "Learning to Write/Hokusais", undated (Box 7, Folder 353)
  - Robert Glück, "Learning to Write/Wiener", undated (Box 7, Folder 354)
  - Robert Glück, "A Little Prison", undated (Box 7, Folder 354a)
  - Robert Glück, Margery Kempe--manuscript, undated (Box 7, Folder 355)
  - Robert Glück, from Paths of Pain, undated (Box 7, Folder 356)
  - Robert Glück, The Purple Men--manuscript, undated (Box 7, Folder 357)
  - Robert Glück, "Robert Duncan", undated (Box 7, Folder 357a)
  - Robert Glück, "Saint Venus", undated (Box 7, Folder 358)
  - Robert Glück, "The Writing Workshop", undated (Box 7, Folder 359)
  - Robert Glück, correspondence, undated (Box 7, Folder 360)
  - Brad Gooch, Jailbait--manuscript, undated (Box 7, Folder 361)
  - Brad Good, published pieces from Jailbait--collection of stories, undated (Box 7, Folder 362)
  - Brad Gooch, poems, undated (Box 7, Folder 363)
  - Brad Gooch, correspondence, undated (Box 7, Folder 364)
  - Brad Gooch, reviews and promotional material, undated (Box 7, Folder 365)
  - Brad Gooch, Jailbait cover artwork, undated (Box 7, Folder 366)
  - Brad Gooch, photos, undated (Box 7, Folder 367)
  - Richard Haasen, manuscript by Haasen and Cooper, undated (Box 16, Folder 367a)
  - Richard Haasen, correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 367b)
  - Richard Haasen, photos, undated (Box 16, Folder 367c)
  - Richard Haasen, ephemera (Box 16, Folder 367)
  - Richard Hawkins, untitled manuscript, undated (Box 7, Folder 368)
  - Richard Hawkins, "Fireweed" by Cooper and Hawkins, undated (Box 7, Folder 369)
  - Richard Hawkins, correspondence, undated (Box 7, Folder 370)
  - Richard Hawkins, clippings, undated (Box 7, Folder 371)
  - Richard Hawkins, reviews., undated (Box 7, Folder 372)
  - Richard Hawkins, untitled manuscript, undated (Box 16, Folder 368a)
  - Richard Hawkins, promotional material, undated (Box 7, Folder 373)
  - Scott Heim, Mysterious Skin manuscript, undated (Box 7, Folder 374)
  - Scott Heim, Mysterious Skin manuscript cont, undated (Box 7, Folder 374a)
  - Scott Heim, Mysterious Skin jacket, undated (Box 16, Folder 378a)
  - Scott Heim, Pulled Under manuscript, undated (Box 7, Folder 375)
  - Scott Heim, White manuscript, undated (Box 7, Folder 376)
  - Scott Heim, correspondence, undated (Box 7, Folder 377)
  - Scott Heim, correspondence cont, undated (Box 7, Folder 378)
  - Bo Huston, The Bath manuscript, undated (Box 7, Folder 379)
  - Bo Huston, The Dream Life manuscript, undated (Box 7, Folder 380)
  - Bo Huston, The Dream Life manuscript cont, undated (Box 7, Folder 380a)
  - Bo Huston, The Listener manuscript, undated (Box 7, Folder 381)
  - Bo Huston, The Listener manuscript cont, undated (Box 7, Folder 381a)
  - Bo Huston, Meditations in Zurich manuscript, undated (Box 7, Folder 382)
  - Bo Huston, plans for a project, undated (Box 7, Folder 383)
  - Bo Huston, Seven Kinds of Pity manuscript, undated (Box 7, Folder 384)
  - Bo Huston, gossip for Bo Huston by Cooper, undated (Box 7, Folder 384a)
  - Bo Huston, in memoriam, undated (Box 7, Folder 385)
  - No folder (Box 7, Folder 386)
  - Bo Huston, memorial newsletter, undated (Box 7, Folder 387)
  - Bo Huston, reviews and card, undated (Box 7, Folder 388)
  - Gary Indiana, correspondence, undated (Box 7, Folder 389)
  - Jim Isermann, exhibition catalogue, undated (Box 7, Folder 390)
  - Jim Isermann, exhibition catalogue, undated (Box 7, Folder 391)
  - Jim Isermann, reviews, undated (Box 7, Folder 392)
  - Jim Isermann, photos, undated (Box 7, Folder 393)
  - Jim Isermann, promotional material, undated (Box 7, Folder 394)
  - Jim Isermann, Correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 391a)
  - Earl Jackson, Jr.; "Campfire", undated (Box 7, Folder 395)
  - Earl Jackson, Jr.; "Death Drives Across Pornotopia", undated (Box 7, Folder 396)
  - Earl Jackson, Jr.; "Explicit Instruction", undated (Box 7, Folder 397)
  - Earl Jackson, Jr.; "Scandalous Subjects" draft, undated (Box 7, Folder 398)
  - Earl Jackson, Jr.; "Scandalous Subjects" manuscript, undated (Box 7, Folder 399)
  - Earl Jackson, Jr.; chapter 6 of Strategies of Deviance, undated (Box 7, Folder 400)
  - Earl Jackson, Jr.; Cooper biography, undated (Box 7, Folder 401)
  - Earl Jackson, Jr.; correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 402)
  - Jamie Jensen, correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 402a)
  - Tom Kalin, Swoon script manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 403)
  - Tom Kalin, correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 404)
  - Mike Kelley, correspondence and promotional material, undated (Box 8, Folder 405)
  - Kevin Killian, Angel by Killian and Bo Huston, undated (Box 8, Folder 406)
  - Kevin Killian, Arctic Summer, undated (Box 8, Folder 407)
  - Kevin Killian, Brother and Sister manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 408)
  - Kevin Killian, "Dennis Cooper", undated (Box 8, Folder 409)
  - Kevin Killian, Father and Son Killian and Josh Cherin, undated (Box 8, Folder 410)
  - Kevin Killian, Great Moments manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 411)
  - Kevin Killian, Homage to Chrissie Hynde manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 412)
  - Kevin Killian, House of Forks manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 413)
  - Kevin Killian, Negative manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 414)
  - Kevin Killian, "On Robert Creeley", undated (Box 8, Folder 415)
  - Kevin Killian, Persiphae manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 416)
  - Kevin Killian, The Range of Freedom by Killian and Glen Helfland, undated (Box 8, Folder 417)
  - Kevin Killian, review of Brad Gooch's Scary Kisses., undated (Box 8, Folder 418)
  - Kevin Killian, untitled manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 419)
  - Kevin Killian, untitled play, undated (Box 8, Folder 420)
  - Kevin Killian and D. Bellamy, Etc., undated (Box 8, Folder 421a)
  - Kevin Kilian, correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 422)
  - Kevin Killian, correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 423)
  - Ron Koertge, poems, undated (Box 8, Folder 424)
  - Ron Koertge, correspondence and cover, undated (Box 8, Folder 425)
  - James Krusoe, "Four Last Poems", undated (Box 8, Folder 425a)
  - James Krusoe, Jungle Girl, undated (Box 8, Folder 425b)
  - James Krusoe, poems, undated (Box 8, Folder 425c)
  - James Krusoe, correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 425)
  - James Krusoe, reviews, undated (Box 8, Folder 425e)
  - Sean Landers; Art, Life and God manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 426)
  - Eric Latzky, manuscript and correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 426aa)
  - Chris Lemmerhirt, correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 426a)
  - Chris Lemmerhirt, ephemera, undated (Box 16, Folder 426b)
  - Chris Lemmerhirt, photos, undated (Box 16, Folder 426c)
  - Gerard Malanga, "Lectures on Creeley" manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 427)
  - Gerard Malanga, poems, undated (Box 8, Folder 428)
  - Gerard Malanga, The Secret Diaries manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 429)
  - Gerard Malanga, NEA rejection letter, undated (Box 8, Folder 430)
  - Gerard Malanga, clippings, undated (Box 8, Folder 431)
  - Gerard Malanga, promotional material and photo, undated (Box 8, Folder 432)
  - Gerard Malanga, photos, undated (Box 8, Folder 433)
  - Gerard Malanga, correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 434)
  - David Margolis, Creative Writing Manuscripts, undated (Box 16, Folder 434a)
  - David Margolis, correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 434b)
  - Michael Matson, manuscripts, undated (Box 8, Folder 435)
  - Michael Matson, photograph proofs of Cooper, undated (Box 16, Folder 434c)
  - Tim Miller, reviews, undated (Box 16, Folder 438a)
  - Tim Miller, correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 435a)
  - Tim Miller, photos, undated (Box 8, Folder 436)
  - Tim Miller, birth certificate and misc, undated (Box 8, Folder 437)
  - Tim Miller, promotional material, undated (Box 8, Folder 438)
  - Bob Mould, correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 439)
  - Eileen Myles, correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 440)
  - Raymond Pettibon, correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 441)
  - Poems dedicated to Cooper., undated (Box 8, Folder 442)
  - Carter Potter, correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 442a)
  - Carter Potter, ephemera and photos, undated (Box 16, Folder 442b)